-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕由cece&飞飞字幕组倾情奉献，严禁用于商业途径
--------------------------
每一个字幕中都浓缩了飞哥对宝贝的爱
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作:飞飞
校对:西西宝贝
--------------------------
爱宝贝的飞哥
为宝贝制作的---爱的字幕
老爸老妈的罗漫史
第一季 第八集
How I met your mother
Season 01 Episode 08
孩子们, 纽约有很多栋楼房
Kids,there are many buildings in new york city.
上千的公寓
Thousands of apartments,
和无数的发生在其中的故事
millions of stories.
尽管已经是十几年前的事了
现在已经不知道是谁住那
And even though it's been decades and someone else lives there now,
那座公寓永远是
对我们而言特殊的地方
there's one apartment in particular that will always be our apartment.
在那我有如此多的美好回忆
I have so many great memories of that place.
Marshall玩电子游戏
Marshall playing video games.
Lily在安全出口那画画
Lily painting on the fire escape.
抱歉, Matson先生
Sorry,mr. Matson.
还有我煮咖啡
And me making the coffee.
这个咖啡壶
I had this coffee pot
已经50岁了
it was probably 50 years old at the time,
煮出来的咖啡真的很难喝
and it made truly terrible coffee.
我们叫他Shocky
We called it shocky.
- 插插头
- 保存
-Plugging in. -Saving game.
我喜欢在那里的每一样东西
I loved every last detail of that place,
用强力胶黏在墙上的两把剑
right down to the incredibly tacky swords we hung on the wall.
永远也不想把它们换下来
I never wanted any of it to change.
但生活并不可能停滞不前
But that's not how life works.
你们肯定想不到
我们刚刚经历了什么
You guys will never believe what just happened to us.
我自己都不敢相信
I don't even believe it myself.
我们在皇后大道
准备顺便去我的公寓看看
We were in queens,and we decided to stop by my apartment.
等等, 她的公寓?我以为Lily阿姨
和你还有Marshall叔叔一起住
Wait,her apartment? I thought aunt lily lived with you and uncle marshall.
我能理解你们为什么这么想
I could see how you would think that,
但是我得有我自己的私人空间
这是独立的问题
but I have to have my own place. It's an independence thing.
上次你去那是什么时候的事了?
When was the last time you were there?
三个月前
Three months ago.
什么? 这就象那些超大的内裤
What? It's like fat pants.
你永远不会想去用它
但只要知道它在那就行了
You hope you never have to use them,but you're glad to know they're there.
- 到底怎么了?
- 怎么了?
-What the hell? -What?
这是我的公寓
This is my apartment.
- 哪儿?
- 就在这
-Where? -Right here.
到底怎么了?
What the hell?
Lily, 这明显是家中国餐厅
Lily,this is a chinese restaurant.
不, 不对, 这里是我的公寓
No,no,this was my apartment.
我的衣橱在那儿...
My dresser was right...
那就是我的衣橱!
that's my dresser!
这里是我的储物间
And this is my closet.
我把指甲屑倒在这
这里还有碎屑
And I spilled nail polh there. There's the stain.
嗨 几位?
Hi. How many?
Lily
Lily.
对 你知道我?
Yes.You know me?
是啊
你的返校节照片
Yeah. From your homecoming picture.
你本人看起来好看多了
You're much prettier in person.
对, 我就知道
不该弄那些刘海
Yeah,I know,the bangs were a mistake.
我的东西呢?!
Where's my stuff?!
噢, 都在后面呢
Oh,it's all in the back.
我们可以帮你打包
你要带走吗?
We could wrap it up for you. You want it to go?
这是我的公寓
This is my apartment.
现在不是了
Not anymore.
没门 你得索要赔偿
No way. You're making this up.
公寓必须得以某种方式
通知你这件事才对
Yeah,the building would have had to give you some kind of notice.
他们给你发通知了
They sent you a notice about this.
- 什么时候?
- 三个月前
-When? -Three months ago.
这些是你的邮件 除去杂志
And here's your mail. Minus magazines.
嗯, 法律上来说他们不能就这样
把你丢在街上 你有租约
Well,still legally,they can't just toss you out on the street. You have a lease.
我是没有书面上的合约
但去问问我的房东 Conroy夫人
Okay,so I didn't have a written lease as such,but go ask my landlady,mrs. Conroy.
她虽然已经98岁了, 但她还是...
She may be 98 years old,but she's still...
她死了, 是吗?
she's dead,isn't she?
甚至没看到巴士
Never even saw the bus.
我的公寓变成了中国餐厅
My apartment is a chinese restaurant.
我要怎么办?
What am I going to do?
来和我们一起住吧
Come live with us.
-真的吗?
-当然
Really? Of course.
你确定同意吗, Ted?
You sure about this,ted?
嗯 我说, 你基本上可以说
是一直住在这了
Yeah. I mean,you basically live here anyway.
不会改变任何事情
It's not like it'll change anything.
错, 这会改变任何事情
No,it's like it will change everything.
噢, Ted, 你太差了
Oh,ted,you are so screwed.
你们在说什么?
What are you talking about?
为什么那女的一直盯着你?
And why is that girl checking you out?
因为我帅
Because I look good.
听好 你和Marshall是室友
Now,focus. You and Marshall are roommates.
你们有间很棒的公寓
Marshall和Lily刚订婚了
You have an amazing apartment. Marshall and lily just got engaged.
那又怎样?
Yeah,so?
那么，当他结婚时你就
不再是他的室友啦, 是不?
So,you're not still going to be his roommate when he gets married,are you?
得有人搬出去
你觉得会是谁呢?
Someone's going to move out. So who's it going to be?
拜托, Barney
他们肯定讨论过谁搬出去
Come on,barney,I'm sure they've talked about who gets the apartment.
你们有谈过这些, 是吗?
You've talked about who gets the apartment,right?
对, 我们是有谈过
Yeah,we've talked about it.
那么我和Lily结婚时
谁会得到这间公寓?
So when lily and I get married,who's going to get the apartment?
噢, 这个很难决定
Oh,that's a tough one.
-你知道谁能解决这问题吗?
- 谁?
You know who I think could handle a problem like that? Who?
未来的Ted和Marshall
Future Ted and future Marshall.
是哦
让他们去解决吧
Totally. Let's let those guys handle it.
该死, 过去的Ted
Damn it,past Ted.
你完蛋了, 小子
You blew it,dude.
Lily已经搬进去了
已经是新的局面了
Now that lily's there,it's a whole new dynamic.
他们要把你挤出去了
They're edging you out.
这不可能
That's crazy.
他们不会把我挤出去
Marshall是我最好的朋友
They're not edging me out. Marshall's my best friend.
我最好朋友之一
one of my best friends.
他不会那样对我的
He wouldn't do that to me.
你小心点就是了
这就是我要说的, Teddy
Just keep your eyes open,that's all I'm saying,Teddy.
你公寓里将有微妙的变化
Little things are going to be changing around that apartment.
拜托, Barney
你想太多了
Come on,Barney,you're just being paranoid.
我说, 那女的到底怎么了?
Okay,seriously,what is this girl's deal?
- 我可以说和她在约会
- 什么?
-I'm sort of on a date with her. -What?
我在网上认识她的
I found her online.
我厌倦了酒吧, 一夜情
I'm tired of the whole bar scene,the one-night hookups.
我在寻找我的最终伴侣
I'm looking for a soul mate.
可以让我去爱去拥抱的人
Someone who I can love and cuddle.
我网上的自我描述是这么说的
Or so it says in my profile.
但是这女孩...
but this girl...
她也想要同样的东西
她...
she wants the same stuff.  And it's...
她让我灰心了
it's bumming me out.
- 好吧, Ted, 从医院打给我
- 好的
-All right,Ted,call me from the hospital. -All right.
你要去医院?
You're going to the hospital?
不是, 他回到那儿
我给他打电话
No. See,he's going to go back over there,and I'm going to call him.
他就装做是家里从医院
给他打的紧急电话
He's going to pretend it's an emergency call from a family member at the hospital.
噢, 天, 假装家里出事?这是
小说里最笨, 最差劲的逃避方式
Oh,lord,fake emergency? That is the lamest,most pathetic cop-out in the book.
- 我对你期望更高点
- 嗯, 还是得这样
-I expect more from you,barney. -Well,stay tuned.
我在试着发现新方法
I'm working on some stuff.
打电话的同时, 祝我好运
But in the meantime,wish me luck.
你要去和Marshall谈谈吗?
So,are you going to talk to marshall?
他会想要那公寓, 我也想要
He's going to want the apartment,I'm going to want the apartment.
这会导致争执
所以我不要谈
It's going to lead to an argument. So.no.
呃, 这很有助健康
Hmm,that's real healthy.
当有问题来临时
你的方式就是躲开?
So when a serious issue comes up,your response is just to avoid it?
我得打电话了
I should really make this call.
噢 我能来吗?
Whoo,can I do it?
你好
Hello.
嗨... 性感小子
Hi,there... sexy.
你好, Cathy阿姨
有什么事吗?
Hello,aunt cathy. What's up?
噢, 没什么
Oh,nothing.
只是坐在这想着你, 辣小伙
Just sitting here thinking about you,hot stuff.
事故?
An accident?
那Rudy叔叔还好吧?
Ll,is uncle rudy going to be okay?
Cathy阿姨身上痒痒
只有你能抓, 大块头
Aunt cathy's got an itch that only you can scratch,big boy.
噢, 天那 为什么他会认为
能自己制造直升机?
Oh,god.Why did he think he could build his own helicopter?
噢, 来吧, 伙计, 把我撕成碎片
Oh,come on,daddy,break me off a piece of that white chocolate.
嗯, 如果他需要移植, 我愿意
Well,if he needs a transplant,he can have mine.
我马上去那
I'll be right there.
你知道... 我...
You know... I...
一会见
see you guys later.
记在我帐上
Put it on my check.
啊, 这会很不错的
我们仨住一起
Ah,this will be nice. The three of us living together.
完美的组合
I think it's a good setup.
天, 这咖啡很不错
Man,this coffee's great.
真的很不错
It's really great.
太棒了
Too great.
shocky怎么了?
What happened to shocky?
这是什么?
What's this?
我从我公寓拿来的咖啡机
My coffeemaker from my apartment.
煮的咖啡很好喝, 不是吗?
It makes great coffee,right?
是啊, 确实
Yeah,definitely.
我是说, Shocky煮的也好喝
I mean,so does shocky.
是吗? 我一直觉得Shocky
煮的咖啡很难入口
Really? I always thought shocky's coffee tasted kind of rusty.
对, 不, 的确
我说, 我有点喜欢那种味道
Yeah,no,it did. I mean,I kind of liked the rusty taste.
我可能习惯那种味道了
我也不知道
I'm used to it,I don't know.
Lily的咖啡机也不会
你知道
Also,lily's coffeemaker doesn't,you know,
震撼人
shock people.
不, 只是... 你得承认它
它... 每天早晨叫你起床
No,it's just... you got to admit that shock,that... wakes you up in the morning.
不知道还有什么
能让你起床吗? 咖啡
You know what else wakes you up in the morning? Coffee.
不错 你是对的
That's great. You're right.
室友们 我喜欢
Roomies. I love it.
他们在挤我出去
他们确实是在挤我出去
They're edging me out. They're totally edging me out.
- 我不敢相信, 但你是对的
- 我就说
I didn't believe it,but you're right.  Told you.
那个Lily
她很精
That lily-- she's a shrewd one.
是啊, 她给你了个
新的咖啡机-- 她怎么敢
Yeah,she got you a nice new coffeemaker-- how dare she.
不只是咖啡机
It's not just the coffeemaker.
完成了 我的画完成了
Done. The painting's done.
- 太棒了
- 很不错
-That is great. -nice
你想挂在哪?
Where do you want to hang it?
我不知道 呃...
I don't know. Uh...
钢琴上?
over the piano?
对哦, 那地方很适合
Yeah,that would be a good place for it.
已经有两把破剑在那了
我们很喜欢那两把剑
Too bad the swords are there. We kind of love those swords.
这两把剑在那已经很久了
Well,those swords have been up there a long time.
我知道, 是不?
我会很想念它们的
I know,right? I'd really miss them,too.
那么放在Marshall的房间吧
So,maybe marshall's room.
好吧
Okay.
他要把那两把剑取下来
He was going to take the swords down.
你们相信吗?
Can you believe that?
Ted, 你干嘛不干脆去和他谈谈
他是你最好的朋友
Ted,why don't you just talk to him. He's your best friend.
最好朋友之一
one of your best friends.
重点是, 这是友好谈判
The point is,maybe it's time for some healthy communication.
友好谈判? 这是最烂的主意
Healthy communication? That's the worst idea ever.
听着, 你开始已经退让过了
这很好
Look,you held off their first advance. That's good.
现在是时候反击了
Now it's time to counterstrike.
我该怎么做?
Well,what am I supposed to do?
你得划分出你的领地
You got to mark your territory.
我不是说不去厕所嘘嘘了
And I don't mean missing the toilet.
你得做点大事件
You've got to do something big.
- 什么?例如买个新沙发
- 更大的
-What,-like buy a new sofa?
-Bigger.
Katie来了
Katie's here.
好吧, 我快点说...
昨晚, 我突然领悟到
Okay,real quick... last night,epiphany--
约会需要的是什么
I realized what the world of dating needs.
准备好?
产品质量法
Ready? A lemon law.
就象给汽车规定的?
A lemon law like for cars?
完全正确
Exactly.
约会开始的一瞬间，你有五分钟
决定是否愿意花上整晚时间
From the moment the date begins,you have five minutes to decide whether you're going to commit to an entire evening.
如果你不愿意, 不会让对方难过
只用说晚上好
And if you don't,it's no hard feelings. Just,"good night.
谢谢参与 永远别见
Thanks for playing. See you never.
哈? 哈? 质量法
这将是个大发明
" Huh? Huh? The lemon law-- it's going to be a thing.
可能的话, 现在就开始执行
Possibly,starting right now.
嗨, Katie
Barney
Hi,katie. Barney.
嗨 终于见到你了
Hi. It's good to finally meet you.
嗯,是啊
Katie, 你将成为历史新篇章
Hmm,yeah. Katie,you are about to be a part of history.
告诉你的朋友们
Tell your friends.
这将是个大发明
It's going to be a thing.
天, Ted最近很奇怪
Man,ted's been acting weird.
他开始标记他所有的食物
He started labeling all his food.
他甚至在那块奶酪上
刻上 Ted
He even carved "ted" into that block of cheese.
是啊 现在成ed了
Yeah. Well,now it's ed'S.
我觉得他不是
很适应我搬进来
I think he's not cool with me moving in.
不, 不是这个
No,that's not it.
你以前就算是住在这了
You've basically lived here all along.
Ted喜欢你
Ted loves you.
他的经前综合症为什么又犯了？
So what's he pmsing about?
我也不知道
I don't know.
他准备和我谈的时候
他就会过来找我谈了
But when he's ready to talk to me about it,he'll come and talk to me about it.
你在开玩笑吗?
你们两什么都没谈过
Are you kidding? You guys never talk about anything.
他不会提起来直到他做出什么怪的事
he'll just let it fester under the surface until he doesn't something big and passive-aggressive.
你一点也不了解Ted
You clearly don't know ted.
Ted Mosby的货物
Delivery for ted mosby.
你的电话亭送来了
Your english phone booth arrived.
噢, 太棒了!
这太棒了, 是不?
Oh,awesome! It's great,right?
是啊, 我只是不确定
Lily会不会喜欢它
Yeah,I guess I'm just not sure if lily's going to like it.
嗯, 我喜欢
所以我要把它放这儿
Well,I like it,so I'm just going to keep it right here,
如果没问题的话
if that's cool.
当然
Of course.
我是说, 我们都住这
所以...
I mean,we all live here,so...
我们得尊重每个人的喜好
we should all be able to have things the way we want them.
对啊
Exactly.
那好 太好了
Great. Terrific.
你喜欢这电话亭
就让它放那
You like the phone booth,it stays.
我喜欢这幅画...
I like this painting...
我要把它挂在...
so I'm just going to hang it...
这面墙上
right here on the wall.
噢 就象这样, 是不?
Mm. Oh. So it's like that,is it?
噢, 你好, 总督
Oh,hello,governor.
噢, 就这样, 对吗? 再见
Oh,it's like that,isn't it? Cheerio.
对, 就这样
Yeah,it's like that.
我想要这间公寓
I want this apartment.
嗯, 我也想要
Well,I want it,too.
你真是个混蛋
You're a jerk.
不对, 我是很有远见的
No,I'm a visionary.
产品质量法! 这将会实现的
Lemon law! It's going to be a thing.
说实话, 你的质量法是这个
浅尝辄止的社会的缩影
For the record,your little lemon law is a symbol of everything that's wrong with our no-attention-span society.
不 错了 质量法是很棒
No. Wrong. Lemon law's awesome.
需要比五分钟更多的
时间才能了解一个人
It takes longer than five minutes to really get to know someone.
你判断一个人太快了
可能会错过很多好东西
You keep giving up on people so quickly. You could miss out on something great.
好吧, 你将要约会
一个没见过的家伙
Okay,you're on a blind date.
坐在对面的... 那家伙
Sitting across from the table is... that guy.
你真需要超过五分钟
来确定没有第二人选了吗?
You really think it'll take more than five minutes to realize there will be no date number two?
是, 我需要
Yes,I do.
我知道的是
那家伙是我的灵魂伴侣
For all I know,that guy's my soul mate.
噢... 你错大了, Scherbotsky
Oh... bad move,scherbotsky.
嗨 见过Robin吗?
Hi. Have you met robin?
- 嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
好了, Marshall，我们来
决定谁将得到这间公寓
All right,marshall,we're deciding right now who gets this apartment.
可能会导致争执
May lead to an argument,
但我们得解决问题
but we're settling this.
- 或者我们可以扔硬币
- 好, 来扔硬币吧
-Or we could flip a coin. -Yeah,let's flip a coin.
- 扔吧
- 好
Flip it. Okay.
- 我要扔了 来了
- 扔啊
-I'm flipping it. Here I go. -Flip it.
- 好, 我要扔了
- 快扔吧
-Okay,here I go. -Flip it.
我扔了
I'm flipping.
我扔之前, 我想说几句
But before I do,I just want to say something.
一开始你甚至不愿意搬进来
You didn't even want to move in here in the first place.
你说战前建筑
对你的过敏不好
You said a pre-war building was bad for your allergies.
那是五年前了
That was five years ago.
现在在药房就能拿到
抗组胺剂的药方
Now you can get prescription-level antihistamines over the counter.
噢, 吧嗒
你还有什么好说的?
Oh,snap. What else you got?
好吧, 我扔了
正面还是反面?
Okay,I'm flipping. Heads or tails?
- 你根本不需要两个房间
- 正面还是反面, Marshall
-You don't need two rooms. -Heads or tails,marshall.
好像你需要两个房间似的
Like you need two rooms.
我们可能很快会组建家庭
We might be starting a family soon.
噢, 不, 你不会
Oh,no,you're not.
你还在念法学院的时候
怎么可能会要小孩
There's no way you're having a baby while you're still in law school.
至少得三年后
It's going to be at least three years.
可能更快我们并没有
很认真的避孕
It could be sooner. We're not that careful with our birth control.
第二次反驳
Two-zip.
噢, 拜托! 你清楚的很
要是我搬走，那间房会空出来
Oh,come on! You know damn well,I move out,that room's going unused.
噢, 假设你找到新的室友
应该会是, Barney?
Oh,and I suppose you'll get a new roommate. who's it going to be,barney?
你知道他做饭时是裸体
You know he cooks naked.
但至少Barney不会把剑取下来
Yeah,well,at least barney wouldn't take the swords down.
我们是兄弟!
We were bros!
这两把剑代表我们的兄弟情
These swords represent our bro-hood.
但你却想把它换上
你的未婚妻的蠢画?
And you took them down to make room for your fiancee's stupid painting?
我未婚妻? 怎么突然
称呼她为未婚妻了?
My fiancee? Suddenly she's "my fiancee"?
Lily是我的一部分
Lily's a part of who I am.
如果我们是兄弟
她也就是你的一部分
Anif you're such a bro,she's a part of who you are,too.
她是兄弟的一部分
She's a bro by extension.
这公寓是我应得的
Marshall
I deserve this apartment,marsall.
没有我应该
No more than I do.
好 那我们扔硬币吧
Great. So let's flip for it.
扔吧!
Flip it. !
所以，这就是我们决定谁得到公寓的方法?
So, is this how we're deciding who gets the apartment?
我也这样想
I guess so.
我们要怎么决定?
How are we doing this exactly?
就这样, 打到死?
Is this,like,to the death?
我们得算出来
We shod probably figure that out.
他没事, 他没事
He's okay,he's okay.
我能说点什么吗?
Can I observe something?
这很棒不是吗?
That this is kind of awesome?
是的
Totally.
- 我们怎么不早这样呢
- 我知道
-I can't believe we didn't do this before. -I know.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我和一位刚认识的美丽女士
在我最喜欢的餐厅用餐
I'm sitting here with a beautiful woman I just met eating at my favorite restaurant.
很甜蜜
Sweet.
这是个好地方
It's a nice place.
很高兴知道未来也有排骨
It's good to know the future has ribs.
在未来, 食物很可能
是装在雷管里的
In the future,food will most likely be served in gel cap form.
另外, 那时候奶牛
可能已经灭绝了
Plus,cows will probably have died out by then.
或者成为我们的统治者
Or be our leaders.
- 你好
- 嘿嘿嘿嘿
-Hello. -H-h-h-h-hey.
时间到了, Scherbotsky
Time's running out,scherbotsky.
最后一次使用质量法的机会
Last cnce for the lemon law.
- 别烦我
- 4:56, 4:57, 4:58...
-Leave me alone. -4:56,4:57,4:58...
我们才刚开始了解对方
we're only just getting to know each other.
说我是对的
这些就能结束啦
Say I'm right and this could all be over.
这可以成为医院
来的紧急电话
This could be your call from the hospital.
让我猜猜，有个疯狂的事故
导致你必须离开
let me guess-- there's been a crazy accident and you have to go.
不, 我绝对不会那样做
No,I would never do that.
我哪也不想去
I don't want to go anywhere.
我是你的了
I'm all yours.
听着, 如果你是妓女
我没那么多钱...
Look,if you're a hooker,I don't have a lot of money...
- 噢, 这太棒了
- 我知道
-oh,that was awesome. -I know.
再来一次
Do it again.
好吧 但这次你跳起来
我袭击你的腿
Okay. But this time jump up and I'll swipe your legs.
听着... 你知道为什么
我得拥有这地方？
look... here's why I should get the place.
你和Lily, 你们要结婚的
You and lily,you get to be married.
我得到什么呢, 是不?
What do I get,right?
我没人结婚, 孤单一人
少了两个室友
I get to be unmarried,alone,minus two roommates.
重点是, 我会无家可归
And on top of that,I have to be homeless.
这公平吗?
Does that seem fair?
噢, 想的美
Oh,boo-freakin'-hoo.
什么?!
What?!
我呢
Woe is me.
"我还没有结婚
我的卵巢在萎缩"
"I'm not married yet. My ovaries are shrinking."
Ted! 如果你现在想结婚
你可能结的, 但是你不想
Ted! If you wanted to be married by now,you would be,but you're not.
你知道为什么吗?
因为你太吹毛求疵啦
And you know why? Because you're irrationally picky.
你太容易分心
和失去兴趣啦
You're easily distracted and you're utterly anhedonic.
- 失去兴趣?
- 失去兴趣
-"Anhedonic"? -Anhedonic.
我的意思你不能享受事情
It means you can't enjoy anytng.
我不能吗
The hell I can't.
- 我在享受这个
- 我知道 这些规则!
-I'm enjoying this. -I know. This rules!
我很抱歉我把剑拿下来了
I'm sorry I took those swords down.
伙计, 没事
Dude,that's okay.
这让我们能玩剑击
不是吗?
It lead to this totally rad swordfight,didn't it?
是啊, 确实
Yeah,it did.
你记得我们刚得到这两把剑的时候吗?
you remember when we first got these swords?
是我们搬进来的那天
It was the day we moved in.
恭喜, Marshall, 我们住在
一个墙上有挂剑的公寓
Congratulations,marshall,we live in an apartment with swords on the wall.
单子上的梦想
现在实现一半啦
List of lifelong dreams,you're now half as long.
糟糕, 我弄掉了
这桌子的一个螺丝钉
Crap,I'm missing one of the screws for this table.
用胶粘吧
Just use this wood glue.
粘的住
It'll hold.
噢天那, 我马上去
Oh god, I'll be right there.
Kevin, 我很抱歉 我得走了
Kevin,I'm so sorry. I have to go.
我的朋友被剑刺伤了
My friend's been stabbed with a sword.
Hab slosi' quch!
这样很不礼貌 你不尊重我
It's a klingon insult. You have no honor.
你知道, 如果你觉得要走
你可以坦诚相对
You know,if you felt this way,you could've just been upfront.
不, 我发誓, 这是真的 我...
No,I swear,that was a real call. I just...
噢, 算了
oh,forget it.
我刺伤了Lily
I stabbed lily.
我刺伤了我的未婚妻
I stabbed my fiancee.
别这样, Marshall
Come on,marshall,
你真觉得她还是
你的未婚妻吗?
do you really think she's still your fiancee?
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
嘿, 我认为你们
应该得到公寓
Hey,I think you guys should have the apartment.
但是你如此勇敢的为它而战
But you fought so bravely for it.
我不是为公寓, 我是为...
I wasn't fighting for the apartment,I was fighting for...
我不知道... 为了让
所有的东西保持原状
I don't know... for everything to stay the way it is.
但是我不用得到它, 那么...
But I'm not going to get that,so...
认真的, 收下吧, 是你们的了
seriously,take the place,it's yours.
她还好吧?
Is she okay?
医生在给她包扎 她会没事的
They're just patching her up. She's going to be fine.
那么听好 我正要和
这女孩约会, Jackie...
So get this: I was on a date with this girl,jackie...
怎么? 你们说她不错啊
what? You said she's fine.
那么无论如何
我和这女孩在约会, Jackie...
So anyway,I was on a date with this girl,jackie... wow,jackie,you make a really great first impression.
哇, Jackie, 你给
我很好的第一印象
wow,jackie,ou make a really great first impression.
我觉得今晚你的结束语
会是...
I have a feeling that tonight you might end up being jackie...
嗯 很抱歉, 我得用
质量法来评判你
Yeah. I'm sorry,I'm going to have to lemon law you.
已经传播出去了
这会实现的
It's out there. It's a thing.
质量法是伟大的发明!
The lemon law is a thing!
该死, 我应该叫它Barney法
Damn,I should've called it barney's law.
- 但你完全...
- 让他沉醉下吧
-But you totally... -just let him have this one.
好了
All set.
她说她想见质量不合格的
“圆桌”骑士
She said she'd like to see the knights of the poorly constructed roundtable?
是我们
That's us.
剑击?
A swordfight?
抱歉, Lily
Sorry,lily.
星期一, 我要去教导我班上的
On monday,I'm going to have to tell my kindergarten class,
小朋友不要拿着利器跑
who I teach not to run with scissors,
我的未婚夫就是这样刺穿我的
that my fiancee ran me through with a frickin' broadsword.
嗯, 公平的说
并没有把东西刺穿
Well,just to be fair,it didn't go all the way through.
我很抱歉, 现在是在讨论
你刺伤我的程度吗?
I'm sorry,is this a discussion of the degree to which you stabbed me?
你是对的
You're right.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们在为谁能拥有
这间公寓而战, 我赢了
We were fighting to see who gets the apartment,and I won.
呃, 你没有
Uh,you didn't win.
我... 呃... ... 把它让给你的
I... uh... ...gave it to you.
- 你知道吗...?
- 等等, 等等
-You know what...? -Wait,wait,wait.
我并不想要那公寓
I don't want that apartment.
那是男孩子住的
It's a boy apartment.
那里...
充满着剑和电子游戏还有...
It's... full of swords and video games and...
闻起来象男生的味道
kind of smells like dude.
我的意思是, 现在住那很好
但是我们结婚后
I mean,it's fine for now,but when we get married,
我想和你开辟新的生活
……在新的地方
I want to start a new life with you... in a new place.
会想念老地方的
Gonna miss the old place.
我也会
I will,too.
但是我们大概一年内
都不会结婚
But we're not going to get married for,like,a year.
是啊, 那是未来的
Marshall的问题
Yeah,that's future marshall's problem.
让他去处理那些吧
Let that guy deal with it.
是啊
Totally.
可能是失血过多
的原因, 我饿了
Maybe it's the massive blood loss talking,but I'm starving.
我们去吃东西吧
Let's go get some dinner.
我知道个地方
I know just the place.
中国餐厅 我还是不敢相信
Chinese restaurant. I still don't believe it.
我就说吧
I told you.
嘿, 干杯 生活是多变的
Hey,a toast. Life is full of changes.
某天你有间公寓, 下一天
可能就变成卖饺子的了
One day you have an apartment,the next day it's a house of dumplings.
但是重要的东西不会改变
But the important stuff doesn't change.
为重要的东西而干
To the important stuff.
干杯
Here,here. Cheers. Cheers.
为质量法而干
And to the lemon law.
自己和自己干
Self click.
还有, 这是我买的杯子
And by the way,I bought these glasses.
在宜家买的
Bought them at ikea.
这些是我的杯子!
These are my glasses!
我喜欢这首歌
好久没听过了
I love this song. I haven't heard this in forever.
这是你大二时候
给我做的混合磁带
And I'm pretty sure this is a mix tape you made me in sophomore year.
对, 是哦
Yeah,right.
Lily, 你的公寓有
最好的上海饺子
Lily,your apartment makes the best shanghai dumplings.
我爱你, Lily派
1998年情人节快乐
I love you,lily pad. Happy valentine's day 1998.
------------------
爱的字幕
--------------------------
与宝贝一起经营
******       ******
**********   **********
************* *************
*****************************
***************************
***********************
*******************
***************
***********
*******
***
*
How I met your mother
Season 01 Episode 08